Guide to the Ayers family plantation history collection, circa 1850-2015 MS 635
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Ayers family plantation history collection
1850-2015
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Martin, Ann
MS 635
65 Linear Feet 62 boxes
1.19 Gigabytes Tiff images and a PDF summary document of clothing items in the Ayers Family collection (identifier # MS0635aip_001).
This collection includes biographical information about individuals in the Ayers, Brown, McCarty, Martin, Diller, Boettner, Crump, Raynor, Ball, Freytag, and Bergeson, and families, among others. The bulk of the collection involves the life and careers of this kinship network, and their commerce, ministries, and artistic work product, and events ranging from the mid 19th century to the mid 20th century. Some documentary history of the Jitney Jungle grocery chain is included.
Biographical / Historical
The Ayers, Brown, McCarty, Martin, Diller, Boettner, Crump, Raynor, Ball, Freytag, and Bergeson, and families, from the mid 19th century to the mid 20th century. Branches of the allied families moved from the mid-Atlantic states of Pennsylvania and New Jersey westward to Illinois, Ohio, and Iowa, with some Ayers and McCarty families relocating permanently in Mississippi and Texas. Prompted by an interest in Southern agriculture, a Southern migration included the ownership and operation of two post-Reconstruction plantations, located in Mississippi and Louisiana.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes biographical information about individuals in the Ayers, Brown, McCarty, Martin, Diller, Boettner, Crump, Raynor, Ball, Freytag and Bergeson, families, among others. The bulk of the collection involves people and events ranging from the mid 19th century to the mid 20th century.
The collection of photographs, letters, business records, war memorabilia, vintage fashion wardrobe, costumes, books, oral history interview, and objects of art serve to document the life and times of the Ayers family and allied families. Photo-journals, scrapbooks, real estate and legal documents, maps, as well as wardrobe items created by, for, and about the allied families cover their personal and professional lives. The kinship networks cover a geographic range from the U.S. Mid-Atlantic states to the Midwest, and into the Deep South of the 19th and early 20th century. Venturing from family careers in banking, medicine, and textiles, a branch of the family migrated South and pursued commerce and professions including Southern agriculture, church ministries, and academia. This branch of the Ayers, Brown, and Martin families moved from Illinois to Mississippi just before the U.S. officially entered World War I. The collection includes material from the kinship network of the allied families as family members moved within the New Jersey/New York region, the Midwest, the American Great Plains and the Deep South from the 19th century into the 1960s. Well-preserved original materials, as well as copies, serve as evidence of a narrative and material history of the allied families' land, houses, commercial businesses, professions, personal possessions, travels, and holdings, as well as information about various sources of income and assets. Business and personal records document the transfers and the chain of possession of both assets and material collections as they were inherited and inventoried in successive generations. References and materials related to the artistic, literary, and philanthropic work of family members are cross-referenced to other collections.
An 1889 wedding quilt in a crazy-quilt pattern of silk ribbons, velvet, and other textile materials is well preserved, along with the names and faces of each young woman (friends of the bride) who contributed the material and labor.
Several Ayers family members served in The Great War/World War I, and the collection contains photographic, telegraphic, textile, and other documentation of the military service, including documentation of experiences in training, domestic and foreign assignments, medals, uniforms, repatriation and return to civilian life.
Due to a family interest in photography and photographic equipment, the Ayers collection contains a chronological sampling of various types of photography (tin type, negative and positive, sepia toned, black and white, color, slides, and various types and sizes of prints, many numbered, indexed and/or with the identifying tags or labels from exhibits. The photography is the work product of several family members. Aspects of commercial agriculture are detailed in the records of the Ayers family short-lived venture into Southern plantation ownership. The documentation of their management, losses, real estate holdings, labor and leasing practices, capital investments, environmental and natural disaster conditions, transportation and commerce is provided in some detail.
Records from careers in academia, civil engineering, medicine, the Presbyterian ministry, banking, transportation, art history and philanthropy are interspersed throughout the collection. College and university material including yearbooks, notebooks, academic papers, and photography from several institutions in Illinois, Wisconsin, Iowa, Ohio, Missouri and Mississippi - primarily in the first half of the 20th century - are included. Flooding along the Mississippi River basin is documented and commented upon. Diaries, sermons, tape recordings, an oral history interview, calendars, legal documents, receipts, and letters connect various people to their inventories of ration books, vintage cigar boxes, recipes, magazines, wedding and funeral items, political affiliations, sermons, and academic report cards through the decades. Travels (in war, for business, for medical rehabilitation, leisure, and scouting) ranging from the World War I era through the 1950s are well documented by private photography and letters, as well as commercial postcards, marked maps, brochures, and receipts. Skeleton keys, inventories of furnishings, scripts and playbills, costumes, a bust, art exhibit brochures, souvenirs and published literature mark the artistic output of the family members, as well as consumer taste. The oral history interview extends through the Vietnam War era and the disaster of Hurricane Katrina, as experienced in Mississippi by the interviewee.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was donated by Ann Martin of the Ayers family, in 2015.
Index Terms
Subjects
Plantation life; World War (1914-1918); Plantations
Document Types
letters (correspondence); photographs; slides (photographs); military uniforms; business records; interviews; Oral histories
Places
Southern States
Subjects (Persons)
Martin, Ann
- Series I: Clothing (boxes 1-37)
  - Black double-breasted jacket (wrc05918) (Box 1)
  - White skirt (wrc05919) (Box 1)
  - Maroon blouse (wrc05920) (Box 1)
  - White blouse (wrc05921) (Box 1)
  - Sleeveless white and red gown (wrc05922) (Box 2)
  - Red tailcoat (wrc05923) (Box 2)
  - Red blouse with cream hem (wrc05924) (Box 2)
  - White blouse with blue stripe on right sleeve (wrc05925) (Box 2)
  - Blouse with dotted collar (wrc05926) (Box 3)
  - Cream chiffon blouse (wrc05927) (Box 3)
  - Cream blouse with lace trim on collar (wrc05928) (Box 3)
  - White blouse w/ lace details (wrc05915) (Box 4)
  - Ivory dress (wrc05916) (Box 4)
  - Cream walking suit (wrc05917) (Box 4)
  - Argyle pattern purple blouse (wrc05929) (Box 5)
  - White blouse with cinched waist, flared hem (wrc05930) (Box 5)
  - White blouse with scalloped hems and marbled buttons (wrc05931) (Box 5)
  - White dress (wrc05932) (Box 6)
  - Light pink blouse (wrc05933) (Box 6)
  - White blouse (wrc05934) (Box 6)
  - Child's vest (wrc05935) (Box 7)
  - White camisole blouse with lace trim and front buttons (wrc05936) (Box 7)
  - White brassier (wrc05937) (Box 7)
  - White camisole with lace and ribbon trim (wrc05938) (Box 7)
  - White camisole with lace trim (wrc05939) (Box 7)
  - White chiffon shrug (wrc05940) (Box 7)
  - White lace dress with flower embellishments on collar (wrc05941) (Box 8)
  - White petticoat with lace trim (wrc05942) (Box 8)
  - White blouse with embroidery on torso and sleeve hems (wrc05943) (Box 8)
  - White blouse with square sailor-style collar (wrc05944) (Box 8)
  - White petticoat with ruffled hem (wrc05945) (Box 9)
  - White lace dress with tiered skirt and sleeves, and cream ribbon trim (wrc05946) (Box 9)
  - Black lace dress (wrc05947) (Box 10)
  - Black lace and satin dress (wrc05948) (Box 10)
  - Black lace shrug (wrc05949) (Box 10)
  - White petticoat with lace trim and pink ribbon (wrc05950) (Box 10)
  - White dress with ruffled hems (wrc05951) (Box 10)
  - White blouse (wrc05952) (Box 11)
  - White satin blouse (wrc05953) (Box 11)
  - Cream blouse (wrc05954) (Box 11)
  - Cream lace shrug (wrc05955) (Box 11)
  - Women's black overcoat (wrc05956) (Box 12)
  - Plain white petticoat (wrc05957) (Box 12)
  - Navy velvet skirt (wrc05958) (Box 13)
  - Longsleeve black dress (wrc05959) (Box 13)
  - White satin chemise (?) (wrc05960) (Box 13)
  - Tan plaid skirt (wrc05961) (Box 14)
  - Tan plaid jacket (wrc05962) (Box 14)
  - White lace dressing gown (wrc05963) (Box 14)
  - Peach lace gown with pearl brooch (wrc05964) (Box 15)
  - Silver gown with embroidered bodice (wrc06048) (Box 15)
  - Green mesh skirt with gold trim and gold belt (wrc06049) (Box 15)
  - Green mesh shrug with sequins (wrc06050) (Box 15)
  - White cream dress (wrc05976) (Box 16)
  - Black velvet cumberbund/corset (wrc05977) (Box 16)
  - Yellow shorts and bodice with bead tassels (wrc05978) (Box 16)
  - Olive green longjohns, costume (wrc05979) (Box 16)
  - White flower print skirt (wrc05980) (Box 16)
  - White flower print blouse (wrc05981) (Box 16)
  - Women's navy overcoat (wrc05982) (Box 17)
  - Brown plaid waistcoat (wrc05983) (Box 17)
  - Women's navy coat (wrc05984) (Box 17)
  - White blouse with rainbow stripes on sleeves (wrc05985) (Box 18)
  - Red skirt with rainbow stripes (wrc05986) (Box 18)
  - Straw bonnet with pink ribbon trimming (wrc05987) (Box 18)
  - Pink ribbon sash (wrc05988) (Box 18)
  - White skirt with ruffled hem (wrc05989) (Box 18)
  - White skirt with front lacing (wrc05990) (Box 19)
  - White dress with lace trim and tiered skirt (wrc05991) (Box 19)
  - Sleeveless black chiffon dress (wrc05992) (Box 19)
  - Pink skirt (wrc05993) (Box 19)
  - White chemise with ruffled tiered hem (wrc05994) (Box 19)
  - Navy balloon trousers (wrc05995) (Box 20)
  - White pants with blue stripes down sides (wrc05996) (Box 20)
  - White skirt (wrc05997) (Box 20)
  - White blouse with lace panels (wrc05998) (Box 21)
  - White blouse with lace collar, sleeve hems, and back (wrc05999) (Box 21)
  - White chemise blouse (wrc06000) (Box 21)
  - White dress with lace panel stripes on skirt (wrc06001) (Box 21)
  - White drawers with lace hem (wrc06002) (Box 21)
  - White drawers (wrc06003) (Box 21)
  - Black skirt with embroidery and ribbon trim (wrc06004) (Box 22)
  - Black skirt (wrc06005) (Box 22)
  - Cream overskirt with ribbon trim and bow embellishments (wrc06006) (Box 22)
  - Pink nightgown (wrc06007) (Box 22)
  - Black jacket with green embroidery (wrc06008) (Box 23)
  - White naval uniform shirt (wrc06009) (Box 23)
  - Black jacket with lace on shoulders (wrc06010) (Box 23)
  - Black double-breasted overcoat (wrc06011) (Box 24)
  - Black topcoat (wrc06012) (Box 24)
  - Beige walking skirt (wrc06013) (Box 24)
  - Black frock with decorative cording (wrc06014) (Box 25)
  - Black and cream blouse with lace collar and sleeves (wrc06015) (Box 25)
  - White vest with lace and pink ribbon (wrc06016) (Box 25)
  - Red and tan chevron knitted skirt (wrc06017) (Box 25)
  - Black jacket with large white octagonal buttons (wrc06018) (Box 25)
  - Black jacket with brown lining (wrc06019) (Box 26)
  - White petticoat with layered hem (wrc06020) (Box 26)
  - White petticoat (wrc06021) (Box 26)
  - White dotted blouse and skirt (wrc06022) (Box 27)
  - White dress with embroidered skirt and lace sleeve hems (wrc06023) (Box 27)
  - Ivory blouse with embroidery (wrc06024) (Box 27)
  - Ivory chemise with embroidered hem (wrc06025) (Box 27)
  - White vest with ribbon trim, and matching sashes (wrc06026) (Box 28)
  - White petticoat with lace stripe (wrc06027) (Box 28)
  - Blue and white polka dot blouse and skirt (wrc06028) (Box 28)
  - Navy riding jacket with frog closures (wrc06029) (Box 29)
  - White linen vest missing buttons (wrc06030) (Box 29)
  - White linen vest (wrc06031) (Box 29)
  - Ivory knit two piece dress (wrc06032) (Box 30)
  - Tan blouse with bones (wrc06033) (Box 31)
  - Mint and rose blouse bead ornamentation (wrc06034) (Box 31)
  - Chocolate velvet coat with tassels and tails (wrc06035) (Box 32)
  - Green knit two piece dress (wrc06036) (Box 33)
  - Green knit cardigan (wrc06037) (Box 33)
  - Sienna and pink dress with embroidery (wrc06038) (Box 33)
  - Dress with white bodice and black skirt (wrc06039) (Box 33)
  - Forest green fit and flare coat with balloon sleeves (wrc06040) (Box 34)
  - Child's red jacket (wrc06041) (Box 34)
  - Red dress with cut outs (wrc06042) (Box 34)
  - Black petticoat (wrc06043) (Box 35)
  - Black mesh overskirt (wrc06044) (Box 35)
  - Black skirt with brown lining (wrc06045) (Box 35)
  - Purple skirt (wrc06046) (Box 36)
  - Purple jacket (wrc06047) (Box 36)
  - White apron with front pocket (wrc06051) (Box 37)
  - White shawl with lace trim and sleeve hems (wrc06052) (Box 37)
  - Black cumberbund (wrc06053) (Box 37)
  - French maid costume accessories (wrc06054) (Box 37)
  - Black bodice and apron with painted flowers (wrc06055) (Box 37)
  - Light blue and pink skirt (wrc06056) (Box 37)
  - Digital images of Ayers Family collection clothing items and summary descriptive document
- Series II: People (photographs, genealogies and ephemera, boxes 38-39)
  - Ayers Family genealogical manuscripts (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Augustus Sidney Ayers declaration re Ayers family history, 2002
    - Transcript of Oral History of Esther Mary Ayers, undated
    - Family-generated timelines; provenance documentation of quilts, 2004
    - "It's Your Story, Pass it On" workbook pages completed by Esther Mary Ayers
    - End-of-life management of Esther Mary Ayers in Houston, Texas
    - Research notes
  - Ayers family birth, marriage, death documentation and evidence (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Ceremonial marriage certificate for Augustus Marshall Ayers and Clara Brown
    - Receipt for burial marker for August Marshall Ayers, 1930
    - Memorial Speech at Funeral of Augustus Marshall Ayers
    - Memorial Resolution by the Vicksburg Ministerial Association honoring Augustus Marshall Ayers
    - Certified death certificate of Augustus Townsend Ayers, Illinois, 1953
    - Copies of Bible pages of Birth, Marriage, and Deaths
    - Annulment of first marriage of Edward H. Ayers, Mississippi, 1920
    - Telegrams, clippings, photographs re death and burial of Harman Allan Ayers, 1949
    - News clipping and lyrics found in Harman Ayers' belongings
    - Funeral expenses receipts for Mary Brown Ayers, Mississippi, 1944
    - Obituary of Jonathan Roland Diller, Illinois, 1949
    - Obituary of Fred O. Rixleben, Illinois, 1991
    - E.A. Ayers family china (note card regarding disposition as of 1992)
    - "Augustus Marshall Ayers and the Ayers family in Mississippi" - draft of genealogical sketch written by Laura McDonald in 1957
    - Newspaper clippings announcing marriage of August Townsend Ayers & Esther Mary Martin, 1918
    - Wedding announcement of Augustus Townsend Ayers & Esther Mary Martin on cardstock, 1918
    - Ceremonial marriage certificate, ribbons, Anna, Ill. City Clerk's office envelope re wedding of August Townsend Ayers and Esther Mary Martin
    - Augustus Edward Ayers and Anna E. Diller Ayers Crystal Wedding Anniversary, Illinois, 1867
    - Draft of obituary of Augustus Townsend Ayers, Illinois, 1953
  - Ayers family photographs and ephemera (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Ann Elizabeth Ayers, ca. 1954-1985
    - Augustus Edward Ayers, ca. 1850-1880
    - Augustus Marshall Ayers and family, Illinois, ca. 1880-1918 (also including Shaw family members, Mississippi)
    - Augustus Sidney Ayers and family, ca. 1920-1992
    - Augustus Sidney Ayers and family including grandchildren, ca. 1940s-1990s.
    - Memorial Service program for August Sidney Ayers, Houston TX, 2003
    - Group photo of sales force, including Augustus Townsend Ayers, 1948
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers club membership cards
  - Ayers family photographs (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Clara Elizabeth Ayers, Illinois, 1890s-1942
    - David Ball Ayers oil painting (photograph of, possibly ca. 1825)
    - Edward H. Ayers ("Bud"), Illinois and Mississippi, ca. 1893-1917
    - Esther Mary Ayers, 1940s-1990s
    - Harmon Allen Ayers and others, ca. 1920s-1940s
    - Jane Allison Ayers and others, Pennsylvania, 1980s-1990s
    - M. P. Ayers, Mr. and Mrs., late 1800s
    - Ayers/McCarty family group, ca. 1940
  - Augustus Townsend Ayers family photographs (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Mollie Brown Ayers and baby Augustus Townsend Ayers, circa 1890
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers, Illinois,1891 (1 year old)
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers, Illinois, 1891-1892
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers and Edwards Howe Ayers, Illinois, 1893
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers, circa 1892-1893
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers, in uniform, 1918
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers, Great War service, 1918-1919
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers, 1919
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers, undated, to end of life
    - Augustus Townsend Ayers and family, Illinois and Mississippi, 1890s-1950s
  - Augustus Townsend Ayers scrapbook, Carroll College, 1909-1910 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Augustus Townsend Ayers journal (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Townsend and Clarabeth Ayers photo essay of people, homes, laborers, ca. 1910-1920s (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Esther Mary Ayers photographs (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Esther Mary Ayers journals, 1933, 1936, 1949-1950, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Ayers - Martin wedding announcements in newspapers, 1918 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Esther Mary Ayers, slideshow used at funeral, death certificate (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Esther Mary Ayers and Sidney Ayers, list of life accomplishments (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Esther Mary Ayers' role in Presbyterian Church leadership (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Bergeson Family photographs (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - "Betts" Bergeson, ca. 1950 and 2002
  - Boettner Family photographs and genealogy (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Boettner family tree from 1838 to 2003
    - Anna Boettner, Illinois, ca. 1880s
    - Frank Boettner, ca. 1880s-1950s
    - Frank, Julius, Henry and Otto Boettner in Illinois, early 1900s
    - Fred and Ella Boettner, ca. 1940s
    - George H. Boettner and wife Verna, ca. 1990
    - Henry Boettner, Illinois, ca. 1900-1910
    - Henry, Frank, Ann and Minna Boettner, Illinois, late 1800s
    - Julius and Julianna Boettner family, California, also includes 1891 obituary for Johann Carl Julius Boetnner
    - Lenore Boettner, Illinois
    - Margaret Nancy Boettner, bridal portrait, Everett, Washington, 1940
    - Minna, Mary, and Anna Boettner, Illinois, late 1800s
    - Boettner children circa 1930
    - Boettners, late1800s-1997
    - Residence of Julius Boettner in Seattle, Washington, interior view, possibly 1930s
  - Diller Family photographs (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Anne Elizabeth Diller, ca. 1840s-1890s
    - Florence Diller, Illinois, ca. 1937
    - Grace "Gay" Diller, Illinois, possibly ca 1850
  - Freytag family photographs (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Eliza Freytag Ayers, Illinois -- photographs and 1940 newsletter regarding her 1868 donation of proerty for the Passavant Memorial Hospital
  - Martin Family photographs and documents (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Esther May Martin's commencement announcement – Union Academy, Anna, Illinois, 1912
    - Esther May Martin's early attempts at journaling, 1903-1907
    - Funeral announcement for Dr. S.C. Martin, Anna, Illinois, 1928
    - Photos of friend "Gladys" and the Martins, snapshots of young adults, in scrapbook format, ca. 1908
    - Martin family photos, family gatherings, informal snapshots, garden image, 1940s-1950s
  - McCarty family photographs (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Elizabeth Ayers McCarty, baby portrait in Jackson, Miss. circa 1900; photos through 1972
    - Elizabeth McCarty Edwards' family photos, 1950s-1990s
    - Jane McCarty portrait, Jackson, Miss., ca. 1940s
    - McCarty Family photos, including military service and groups, homes, 1920s-1970s
    - William ("Billy") McCarty as a child
  - Raynor family (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Florence Ayers Raynor photographs, Illinois, ca. 1890s-1910s
  - Rixleben family photographs (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Bruno Rixelben - baby portrait ca. 1900, and family group ca. 1980
    - Elizabeth Rixelben, Illinois, ca. 1940s-1980s
    - Fred Rixelben, pharmacist, Illinois
    - Roy "Rix" Rixelben wedding photographs, 1980s, Oklahoma
    - Tom and Mary __?__Rixelben, also including Boettners, Illinois, ca. 1910-1940
  - Madie Sanford Venerable (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Photos ca. 1910s, and letter to Esther Mary, in 1950, on family business letterhead, Anna, Illinois
  - Associates of Ayers and Martin families (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Three black and white photographs of work activity
    - Don Boyd Stewart – Union Academy, portrait 1912
    - Mailing lists, probably for announcements of marriage of Townsend Ayers and Esther Martin, on A.M. Ayers & Sons Merchants-Planters-Ginners letterhead, Shaw, Mississippi
  - Allied Families – other surnames (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Reimold family, 1990s
    - Townsend family
    - Roger Martin of Houston, Texas, late 20th century
  - Encounters with famous figures (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Townsend Ayers' 1949 account of his service with Dwight D. Eisenhower
    - Willard Givens of National Education Association of the United States writing to Esther M. Ayers, 1949
    - Judge and Nancy Reinholt, 1999
    - US Congressman Paul Simon letter to Esther Ayers, 1975
  - Esther Mary Ayers' participation in H. Ross Perot for President campaign, 1992, and other public policy interests (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Esther Mary Ayers from Barb Brown for Illinois State Senate campaign, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Re-enactment of Lincoln / Douglas debate in Illinois, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Ethel Rhodes McKinley and family photographs, 1940s (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Snapshots found in personal effects of Augustus Sidney Ayers, ca 1940s (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Women's address books, records of family birth dates and anniversaries (kept by Easter Mary Ayers, Minna Ayers, Anna Boettner) (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Sid and Betts Ayers 50th wedding anniversary celebration invitation, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Augustus Townsend Ayers funeral details, 1953, Anna, Illinois (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Anna Magdalena Boettner death announcement and memorial book, Illinois, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Family group photos, Ayers, Boettner, Rexelben reunion photos, circa early 1930s (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Snapshots found in personal effects of Esther Mary Ayers, ca 1970s-1980s (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Photos of unidentified people: WWI soldiers at Fort Logan; WWII baby and housing; band competition; athletes (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - WWI panoramic of Officers, 87th Division, National Army, Camp Pike, 11-24-1917 (Oversize Panoramic box 1)
    - WWI panoramic of soldiers, 08-24-1918, New Jersey (Oversize Panoramic box 1)